

Akmal Muzakki Bakir

Undergraduate Student Data Science at Telkom University

I am a Data Science Student at Telkom University. I was born in jakarta on August 25th, 2003. Experienced in math /programming tutor and problem solving, and is currently focusing on machine learning, creativity code, and mini design.

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE

- Python
- C++
- Go
- Javascript
- HTML & CSS
- Java

DATABASES

- MySQL
- MongoDB

DESIGN

- Fiama
- Adobe After Effect
- Filmora
- Adobe photoshop
- Wordpress

EDUCATION

MAN 1 Kota Bekasi (2018-2021)

• Major: IPA

Telkom University (2021-present)

• Major: Data Science

• IPK: 3.87

EXPERIENCE

Head of Division Social Media Marketing - StudyGez

Math Tutor (volunteer) - Ganesha Operation November 2020 - April 2021

Math Tutor (volunteer) - StudyGez

Lead of Division CODING - ISLAH LDK Al-Fath Telkom University

August 2022 - November 2022

Assistent Lecturer Discreate Math - Faculty of Informatics

March 2023 - Present

Assistent Lecturer Programming Algorithm - Faculty of Informatics

March 2023 - Present

Staff Ministry of Professional Development - Student Association of Telkom University

March 2023 - Present

Staff Ministry of Professional Development - Student Association of Telkom University

March 2023 - Present

ACHIEVEMENT

- 3rd winner of district-level mathematics KSM (2020)
- Final round participant of the 31st LMNas UGM (2019)
- Final round participant of OPTIKA UIN Jakarta (2020)
- Participant of GEOLYMPIC ITS 2020
- Participant of CPC Compfest 14 2022

BASIC SKILLS

- Machine Learning
- Data Analysis
- Data Visualization
- Deep Learning

LIBRARY MOST USED

- Pandas
- Sklearn
- Numpy
- Keras
- Tensorflow
- Seaborn
- Pyplot
- Plotly

OTHER SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Math & Logic
- Statistics and Probability
- Microsoft & Google Tools

SOCIAL MEDIA

Email

- akmalm2003@gmail.com
- akmalmzkki@student.telkomuniversity.ac.id

Phone

• 088292113638 (Whatsapp)

Instagram

• @akmal_mzkki

LinkedIn

• Akmal Muzakki

Github

• akmalmzkki